That's insane.
Heat.
[music]
[music] Heat.
>> [music]
>> Hi vlog.
I'm really going for it tonight with the
checkers and the red car.
I'm just checking in. This vlog I feel
like is well I kind of I knew I wanted
to like capture this trip but I didn't
know whether I wanted to like vlog and
post it because I just want to be like
present and enjoying myself basically.
really felt like I needed this trip to
like switch off and just I wanted to
come here. So, just to like really enjoy
it, but also knew how like amazing it
would be and how I'm going to want to
watch this back and like show people and
just capture the how beautiful
everything is. But I hope you're still
enjoying. I love like videos like this.
Like before I go to bed at night, I
watch camping videos, trips like this,
just anything like calming. I hope this
is like a relaxing watch for you and
that you enjoy it. I know it's probably
a little bit different, but maybe it's
nice. And if you do enjoy it, let me
know cuz I'd love to like capture my
trips in the future. But yeah, it's so
beautiful here. I'm having the best
time. The horse riding this morning was
like actually magical. I was saying to
Greg like I feel like I'm in my books.
Like when we were going through all the
trees and like there was all the
colorful plant uh all the colorful
flowers and like animals and stuff, I
was like this is made up. Like this is
can't be real. But because of the
Canadian wildfires, it is a bit like I
don't know if you've probably like not
noticed, but normally over there you can
see like all of the mountains. I feel
like you could see a bit of this
morning, but yeah, it's definitely
clearer in the mornings and then the
smoke looks like seems a little bit
thicker. Um, but we're up super early
tomorrow to go to Yellowstone, which I'm
like so excited for. I think we're
getting picked up at like 6:30, so I'm
really hoping because we're early, one,
it's clearer, and two, we get to see
some wildlife.
So far, I've only seen elk, which are
wonderful, but I would also like to see
some bison. But yeah, just wanted to
jump in and quickly speak to you [music]
guys.
>> [music]
[music]
>> There's two.
No, just one.
>> Oh, yeah. Wait.
[music]
So, there's 10,000
[music] of these thermal beaches in
Yellowstone. Like nuts.
Wow. Wow. Wow. Look at it go.
>> Wow.
>> That is amazing.
These are my mugs that I'm going to get.
>> This one's for you.
>> This one's for me.
>> What do you think?
>> I love it. Fully support it.
>> 120. Okay.
Let's see.
>> [snorts]
>> 1036.
>> Jeez.
>> Yeah, you definitely don't pop there.
[laughter]
>> You definitely don't want it
>> be very painful.
>> Yeah,
>> I think this is the best view I've ever
seen in my life.
>> [music]
>> We couldn't tell whether it was a wolf
or a coyote,
but it's a coyote. I can confirm.
Thanks,
You can see his nose is like real sharp
and pointed.
>> Yeah.
[music]
This is I think the most [music] insane
lunch spot I've ever had in my life.
Wow.
See the duckies?
cuz they're babies.
The bison are in rot right now, so
they're mating. So, there's loads of
them just all together. Oh my goodness.
Wow.
What a view to get to see them like from
up here.
They are humongous.
Oh
wow.
>> Did I underell it?
>> No.
>> It's like being on another planet.
>> Wa.
>> So today was
insane. Like insane. I can't even put it
into words and I was just looking at the
pictures and like they just don't do it
justice. Like seeing it with your own
eyes was insane. I couldn't even fathom
I what I was seeing most of the time.
But I hope you enjoyed coming along. I'm
ready for dinner now and I want to show
you my outfit cuz it's really cute. I
rented some pieces from the vintage
Mar. I went in there before this trip
and I got this beautiful
baby. She's actually more like pinky.
She looks quite red on here, but she's
actually more of a like,
how would I describe this color? Like a
plum. And then also, I'm wearing them.
So, you're going to see the dogs, but
these Manolos. This is my fit. I don't
even think you can see the full of me.
And these jeans are the rodeo jeans from
Frame. Um they're boot cut and they've
been perfect this trip and they're so
flattering. But yeah, I think it's such
a good idea if you don't want to commit
to pieces and you just want to have them
for a trip or an event or something like
that. Oh, and my top is from I don't
know, but I'll link it. But yeah, time
for some dinner.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Hopefully it's not too loud. I'm outside
and there's a wedding, so there's a bit
of background noise, but should be fine.
Just thought I'd close this off. This
morning was so nice. We went to a hike.
It's called Uso Falls. If you have any
questions about any of the places or
anything, just comment them and I'll
I'll um like write the names and
everything. Also, I put on my Instagram
before I came thinking about getting the
Fujif film because I love my Olympus
like actual film camera and I go through
so many rolls of film on trips and like
obviously sometimes you just don't get
the shot that you wanted and like if you
have like if you like shooting film then
you'll know what I mean. But yeah, it's
just like sometimes a bit temperamental.
Although it's so rewarding and like
beautiful, but I feel like for trips
like this, like I just feel like it's so
nice to be able to shoot as much as you
want as well. And then like and change
the settings and like even just with
things like you know different lightings
and stuff like that. It's just nice to
have like a bit more control. So I mean
I put it on my Instagram and literally
every single answer was like yes, you
should get it. So obviously everyone
that has it loves it. But one of my
friends was like, "I have one. Like, you
can play around with it." I went to his
for dinner. Let me just ask him if I can
borrow it for my trip and like give it a
go and just like see what I think and
stuff. Guys, it's so good. Like, it's so
good. I'm literally going to buy one as
soon as I get home. I wonder if you can
get like surely you can get different
lenses and stuff because obviously the
only thing this trip has been like no
zoom. Um,
but I've loved it just as a point and
shoot. Like I've been like I played
around with the settings before I like
came and before we went on like days out
because I wanted it to be like set up so
I could just like have I just had it
around my neck literally this whole trip
and just was like taking so many
pictures. It's been so fun to shoot with
and like I've been switching like the
film um has like a film simulation
setting and it has like loads of
different settings that you can like
play around with. I used the classic
chrome most of the time. I'm obviously
going to post them on Instagram. So, and
I feel like I might get a lot of
questions on the camera and the
settings. I mean, I can obviously do a
breakdown if anyone's interested, but
it's amazing. This is the V 100V, not
the 100 V1 or 100 VI, so I don't know
how they differ, honestly. I've just
been sitting here looking through the
pictures. I think I'm going to get one
of those books where it's like a trip
book, you know, like a coffee table book
and like put all of the camera pictures
in there cuz I just feel like it would
be so special to look back on this trip.
Even this vlog like I'm going to
treasure like I've been looking at the
clips and like I really will treasure
this vlog and try and relive what I've
gone through this weekend by this vlog.
So, I hope you enjoyed it. I know it
might have been a little bit different
and maybe boring to some people, but I
love watching things like this. So,
yeah, maybe it was something different.
And I hope you found it relaxing or
inspiring to take a trip or something
like that. But I can't wait to just go
to more places in the future. This has
literally been like a once in a-lifetime
trip. Um, we've stayed at the Montage uh
in Big Sky. Would highly recommend. They
are incredible. This whole trip has been
incredible. every single excursion and
guide and like everything has been so
special. I can't it's like I felt so
emotional yesterday because just how
incredible the day was and I just
couldn't believe that I was getting to
experience it and I was getting to see
that. Yeah, I just feel so lucky and so
happy and I really felt like I needed
this trip and yeah, I just feel so lucky
to have experienced what I have the past
few days and I hope you guys felt like
you were along with me for a little bit.
Yeah, I hope you guys have enjoyed and
I'll see you in the next one.